[music]
>> Good morning. It is a little past 5:00
a.m. right now, and I'm going to head
down to get some work done. I've gotten
into the habit of waking up really early
on Saturdays. The past 2 weeks, I was up
like at 4:00.
Today was a little later, but let's head
down and
I'm going to do a practice exam, and
then I'm going to work out, take a
shower, get myself awoke, and we'll go
on with the rest of the day. But, I have
two midterms on the same day this
Tuesday, so we need to study for it
together. So, let's go.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yogurt with Nilla Wafers?
Okay.
Hello. I just finished eating my
breakfast, so now let's get ready. It's
a little past 9:30 now, and the plan for
today is I'm going to go do a little
more studying. Normally, I spend my
entire Saturdays studying and getting
work done, so I can have my Sundays
free, but the plan is a little shifted
today because I have to do deliberations
for interviews that we did for a club
that I'm in, and that's going to be like
4 hours, 3 or 4 hours, which is not fun.
But, that's the thing that I'm doing
today, and at 11:00, I'm first getting
brunch with my friend, which I'm very
excited for. We're going to Tartine,
which is one of my favorite brunch
spots, but I haven't been in such a long
time. So, that's going to be at 11:00,
and then I have deliberations until 3:00
p.m. And then after that, I really need
to lock in and get work done because I
have two finals on the same day on
Tuesday, which is not going to be fun at
all, especially because they're for two
of my hardest classes, and I have
literally no idea what's going on. Like,
trying to do practice tests, and it's
just been so hard. I cannot be bothered.
That's okay, because at least I do have
some good news that happened this past
week, which has made my life a lot
better. So, I believe that everything
will work out, and honestly, grades are
not that deep. I really need to let go
of my obsession with keeping my 4.0. I
feel like I've just been trying not to
care as much anymore, because it's just
so much more freeing, and you live a
much happier life. Let things be, and
let life unfold, because I believe that
the best things are going to happen, and
they always do. So, that's how life
works out for me. Anyways, I'm rambling.
I need to get ready, and then I'm going
to head down to our dining hall, and
then I have about a little over an hour
to get work done.
And today, I'm going to put on this
gorgeous Gucci lipstick. I have have not
like used it a lot since I got it. I
think it's so pretty.
It's so moisturizing, and I really like
the color. Adding some gloss with this
YSL gloss.
Let's head out. Let's go and get work
done. And of course, I can't forget my
crystal bracelets. I genuinely Okay,
like there's definitely a science behind
crystals, because it's something about
like the vibration and the energy and
the ability to vibrate at the same
thing. Like, some sort of scientific
backing to it. But, I swear that it's
actually been helping me so much. I'm
sure it has also to do with like
manifestation and like your subconscious
overall. But, I'm wearing this obsidian
one and also this purple quartz. I'm not
sure what the exact name is. These are
supposed to help you with like your
career and money and school and stuff
like that, and I feel like that's just
been doing wonders for me. And this is
to clean out any negative energy, so I
also love to wear my clear quartz just
for my emotional health and getting rid
of any emotional burden. Okay, I'm all
ready to go. So, let's head out and go
get more work done. Picking my perfume
of the day. I literally got so obsessed
with this Miu Miu perfume. I swear this
perfume smells so good. I'm literally
just like smelling myself all day, which
sounds so weird, but it actually smells
so cozy and I just love it.
Let's go.
Let's head to brunch. [snorts]
Shakshuka.
Yay!
>> [crying]
[music]
>> Hello, it is 5:00 p.m. and I'm finally
back and I got a little sweet treat
because I was feeling like very stressed
and just like not in the right
headspace. Like whenever it gets to
midterm season and it's just a lot going
on.
I got Dubai chocolate froyo and it's
like Greek froyo so it tastes so good.
It's like frozen Greek yogurt. They add
this pistachio sauce and kataifi on the
top. Beautiful. I'm so excited. So, I'm
going to enjoy this little cup and then
I have some frozen fruits.
So, this is my little sweet treat and
then I'm going to rest for the rest of
the night. I normally don't rest on like
Saturdays but because tomorrow I am
going to be locking in. I'm going to be
getting more work done with a friend.
We're going to a cafe and I'll take you
guys along with me because I feel like
this vlog is going to be a little short
if I just end it here. So, we're going
to go and study some more at a very good
cafe with the best matcha, but I'm going
to rest after this. Let's do a quick
taste test before I leave.
>> [snorts]
>> I'll see you in a bit.
Hello. Good morning. It is a little past
10:00 a.m. and I'm up a bit later today
just because first of all, I got always
get up on Sundays very late. Like
usually I'm up at like 11:00. So, this
is quite early, but it's also daylight
savings today. So, we're losing an hour
of sleep. So, it's technically like only
9:00 a.m., but I'm going out to a cafe
with a friend to get studying done for
like the next 7 hours. They have a
really good matcha and I haven't been
out to Boston in like a long time. So,
I'm very excited for that. I don't like
to do makeup on Sundays, but since I'm
going out, let's just do some like
concealer and blush.
Some brow gel.
Bracelets come on. This is pink quartz
and it's supposed to help with
relationships and just overall energy
and vibe. Here's the jewelry for today.
Okay, let's get going and I don't want
to be late. So, I'll see you guys in a
few minutes.
We have a cozy fit today. The top is
from Skims and these sweatpants are from
I think they're from Aerie, maybe. But
let's get going.
Yeah.
No.
Thank you. Of course.
Can you send the pictures to me?
I like how my iPad came
I'm sitting here so pretty.
Look at this little baby.
A lot strawberry.
Finish our matcha. It's 1:37 now. And we
got this truffle sandwich that looks so
delicious. Wow.
Yay.
Sunday Sunday. I'm so excited. Let's get
some ice cream.
Thank you.
Hello, it's 7:00 p.m. and I'm back in my
dorm. After studying with my friend, I
went to get some dinner in my house and
it's Sunday Sunday, so I got some ice
cream and I also got some work done. I
met up with a friend who's also in the
class that I'm in, so we studied a
little for our exam. But now I'm back in
my room.
I picked up a few packages and I'm so
excited, so let's open them together.
OMG,
this is from Blank Street. They recently
released a new sleeve and if you know
me, you'll know how much I love my Blank
Street matcha. Like it's genuinely my
favorite study drink ever. This is so
cute. The packaging is also so pretty.
Wow, look at this insane packaging. Next
is from L'Oreal, which is another one of
my favorite brands. Wow,
look at this. OMG, okay, it's new lip
products, I think.
Oh my god,
this is so pretty. I'm so excited to try
all of this. Thank you so much, L'Oreal.
I bought a few things from Sephora. This
is what I bought. I got the Topicals eye
patches. I've been into using eye
patches recently, so I got these to try
and they're pink, so I'm going to try
this when I study tomorrow morning. I'm
so excited. Amazing. I think I'm going
to end the vlog here because for the
rest of the night I just want to rest,
sleep early and then tomorrow I'm going
to have an early morning and get up and
get some studying done. I've been loving
to study before the sun even rises
recently cuz it's just so quiet and I
feel like I can focus better. But thank
you for spending the weekend with me. It
was so productive and best of luck to
everyone, including myself, on midterms
and I'll see you guys after that. Bye.